<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ME bachelor work</title><link>https://REZuLt-525.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on ME bachelor work</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>zh-cn</language><copyright>LZ</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 20:17:24 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://REZuLt-525.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Description of this site</title><link>https://REZuLt-525.github.io/p/description-of-this-site/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 20:17:24 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://REZuLt-525.github.io/p/description-of-this-site/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="descriptions">Descriptions
&lt;/h1>&lt;p>The 7 projects on this site are the ME related projects I participated in or led during my time in Tonji University. Most of the works are done in the Tongji robot competition team Superpower. In the team, I worked as an ordinary team member of the sentry group in the 2023 season and the mechanical leader of the sentry group alongside the infantry designer in the 2024 season. The project I cooperated with friends all have related descriptions in the passage.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>There are also some ME related experiences, like the interaction with Fudan University and Shihezi University&amp;rsquo;s robot competition team as consultant.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The site may have bugs in other functions, please only read the passages. I have to work on my graduation project when preparing for applications.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Thanks for watching&lt;/p>
&lt;h1 id="the-time-table-for-the-projects">The time table for the projects
&lt;/h1>&lt;img src="https://REZuLt-525.github.io/images/timetable.jpg" alt="123" width="1100" height="200"></description></item><item><title>High-dynamic, wheeled-legged bipedal robot system based on an LQR framework for Whole Body Control</title><link>https://REZuLt-525.github.io/p/high-dynamic-wheeled-legged-bipedal-robot-system-based-on-an-lqr-framework-for-whole-body-control/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 20:17:24 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://REZuLt-525.github.io/p/high-dynamic-wheeled-legged-bipedal-robot-system-based-on-an-lqr-framework-for-whole-body-control/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="brief-introduction-to-the-project">Brief introduction to the project
&lt;/h1>&lt;p>This project is one of the projects in the Shanghai innovation program. For the purpose of tackling more complex terrain and maintaining speed, my teammate and I take a three-cylinder, five-link, two-wheel-leg chassis. This design can also serve as the &amp;lsquo;balance infantry&amp;rsquo; in RoboMaster after slight modifications.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In this project, I was responsible for the mechanical design, including the rod length design of the connecting rod, motor selection, and so on. The electric control part was done by my teammates.&lt;/p>
&lt;h1 id="videos-of-the-design">Videos of the design
&lt;/h1>&lt;p>&lt;video src="https://REZuLt-525.github.io/images/sitp1.mp4" controls="controls" width="500" height="300">&lt;/video>
&lt;video src="https://REZuLt-525.github.io/images/sitp2.mp4" controls="controls" width="500" height="300">&lt;/video>
&lt;video src="https://REZuLt-525.github.io/images/sitp3.mp4" controls="controls" width="500" height="300">&lt;/video>
The video of roll adjustment(top left), moving(top right) and standing up(bottom left) of the robot&lt;/p>
&lt;h1 id="images-of-the-design">Images of the design
&lt;/h1>&lt;img src="https://REZuLt-525.github.io/images/sitp4.png" alt="123" width="400" height="200">
&lt;p>The image of the design of this robot.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Design of a robot based on synchro-drive chassis with a 5 DoF robotic arm</title><link>https://REZuLt-525.github.io/p/the-design-of-a-robot-based-on-synchro-drive-chassis-with-a-5-dof-robotic-arm/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 20:17:24 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://REZuLt-525.github.io/p/the-design-of-a-robot-based-on-synchro-drive-chassis-with-a-5-dof-robotic-arm/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="brief-introduction-of-the-project">Brief introduction of the project
&lt;/h1>&lt;p>The project consist of 4 parts: Mechanical design, PCB design, controlling and visual recognition.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>For the mechanical design, the robot is consisted of two main parts, the chassis part and the gimbal part. The chassis part have four synchro-drive wheel sets and one timing belt driving the first yaw axis of the gimbal. The synchro-drive wheel sets can enable the chassis to achieve omnidirectional movement. To ensure that the robot can manage to operate in more complex conditions, the gimbal part have 5 DoFs, which are yaw-pitch-pitch-roll-yaw respectively. The mechanical design also have the gearbox and wheel set design, which is shown in detail in the related passages.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The PCB in the project serve as the magnetic encoder and distribution board for the heading part of the wheel set.The PCB have two parts. The upper board have the function to turn the high voltage from the chassis main distribution board to the low voltage needed by the M3508 motor on the heading part and driving part of the wheel set, and the ability to pass position information and can bus messages provided by the hall elements from the downwards PCB board. The downwards board have a chip and four hall elements to work with the magnet ring which rotate with the driving part of the wheel set to provide the heading angle information.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>For the control part, I made the kinematic solving of the omnidirectional chassis and made the frame of controlling on the RoboMaster C board (STM32F407IGHx) by using STM32CubeMX. Due to the limit of time, only additional can block and PID block are added. For the gimbal control, the kinematic and inverse kinematic solving of the position of the robotic arm.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I applied the open source YOLO v7 to ensure that the robot have the ability to recognize the context.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Detailed information is shown in the report.&lt;/p>
&lt;h1 id="images-of-the-design">Images of the design
&lt;/h1>&lt;img src="https://REZuLt-525.github.io/images/uiuc1.png" alt="123" width="350" height="200">
&lt;p>The overview of the design of the robot in this project&lt;/p>
&lt;img src="https://REZuLt-525.github.io/images/uiuc2.png" alt="123" width="540" height="200">
&lt;img src="https://REZuLt-525.github.io/images/uiuc3.png" alt="123" width="540" height="200">
&lt;p>The PPT for the PCB design and the proofing of the PCB.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The mechanical design for RM infantry robot, season 2024</title><link>https://REZuLt-525.github.io/p/the-mechanical-design-for-rm-infantry-robot-season-2024/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 20:17:24 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://REZuLt-525.github.io/p/the-mechanical-design-for-rm-infantry-robot-season-2024/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="a-brief-introduction-to--rm">A Brief Introduction to RM
&lt;/h1>&lt;p>The RoboMaster is a robotic competition held by the DJI and later on by the Committee of the Chinese university robot competition.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In the The RoboMaster University Championship (RMUC) , participating teams will independently develop different types of robots with various functions to face off on the battlefield. Each team’s participants will control their robots to attack the opponent’s robots and Base by launching projectiles. At the end of the match, the team with the highest remaining Base HP wins.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>There are overall 7 classes of robots: Hero, Infantry, Engineer, Sentry, Dart system, Radar system and Drone.&lt;/p>
&lt;h1 id="reasons-for-the-redesigning-of-the-infantry">Reasons for the redesigning of the Infantry
&lt;/h1>&lt;p>The former infantry robot used by Tongji Superpower robot competition team is inherited from the 2019 season. That Mecanum wheel-based robot have inevitable problems like the power loss of the wheels, and designing problems like the overweight chassis. Like the 2023 sentry, the magazine&amp;rsquo;s position lead to unnecessary movement of inertia of the gimbal.&lt;/p>
&lt;h1 id="the-detail-for-the-infantrys-mechanical-design">The detail for the Infantry&amp;rsquo;s mechanical design
&lt;/h1>&lt;p>In the sentry project, I developed the gearbox and synchro-drive wheel set, so it is altered to fit the designing requirements of the infantry. Thus the overweight problem of the chassis can be tackled.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The magazine on the gimbal have been replaced to the rotating axis of the yaw pitch. This can help reduce the movement of inertia by at least 40%.&lt;/p>
&lt;h1 id="images-of-the-robot">Images of the robot
&lt;/h1>&lt;img src="https://REZuLt-525.github.io/images/inf2024.jpg" alt="123" width="350" height="200">
&lt;img src="https://REZuLt-525.github.io/images/inf2024_2.png" alt="123" width="350" height="200">
&lt;p>The image of the Infantry and design model of the Infantry, 2024&lt;/p>
&lt;h1 id="videos-of-the-robot">Videos of the robot
&lt;/h1>&lt;p>&lt;video src="https://REZuLt-525.github.io/images/inf2024_3.mp4" controls="controls" width="500" height="300">&lt;/video>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The video of Infantry rotating under 100W power limit of the chassis.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The mechanical design for RM sentry robot, season 2023</title><link>https://REZuLt-525.github.io/p/the-mechanical-design-for-rm-sentry-robot-season-2023/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 20:17:24 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://REZuLt-525.github.io/p/the-mechanical-design-for-rm-sentry-robot-season-2023/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="a-brief-introduction-to--rm">A Brief Introduction to RM
&lt;/h1>&lt;p>The RoboMaster is a robotic competition held by the DJI and later on by the Committee of the Chinese university robot competition.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In the The RoboMaster University Championship (RMUC) , participating teams will independently develop different types of robots with various functions to face off on the battlefield. Each team’s participants will control their robots to attack the opponent’s robots and Base by launching projectiles. At the end of the match, the team with the highest remaining Base HP wins.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>There are overall 7 classes of robots: Hero, Infantry, Engineer, Sentry, Dart system, Radar system and Drone.&lt;/p>
&lt;h1 id="overall-of-the-work-in-the-sentry-robot-2023">Overall of the work in the Sentry robot, 2023
&lt;/h1>&lt;p>The rule for the sentry robot have overgone a dramatic change at the begging of the 2023 season. So the mechanical design of the 2023 sentry robot have to redesign totally.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Considering that the efficiency of the Mecanum wheel sets is relatively low, the chassis choose to develop our own synchro-drive wheel system. Due to the limitations of the competition, this robot have two launching mechanisms which are placed side-by-side. To enable it to build maps and navigate, a MID-360 omnidirectional laser radar is placed at the midst of the yaw axis of the robot&amp;rsquo;s gimbal.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>During the 2023 season, this robot have made the progress from 0 to 1. And thanks to its outstanding performance, our team got the national first prize of the sentry robot.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The detailed design of the wheel sets are shown in another article, since it is used on many robots.&lt;/p>
&lt;h1 id="images-of-the-robot">Images of the robot
&lt;/h1>&lt;img src="https://REZuLt-525.github.io/images/sentry2023.png" alt="图片描述" width="327" height="200">
&lt;img src="https://REZuLt-525.github.io/images/sentry2023_2.png" alt="图片描述" width="300" height="200">
&lt;img src="https://REZuLt-525.github.io/images/sentry2023_3.png" alt="图片描述" width="315" height="200">
&lt;img src="https://REZuLt-525.github.io/images/sentry2023_image.jpg" alt="123" width="220" height="200">
&lt;p>The overview, side and front view of the sentry, 2023 and the image of the robot&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The mechanical design for RM sentry robot, season 2024</title><link>https://REZuLt-525.github.io/p/the-mechanical-design-for-rm-sentry-robot-season-2024/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 20:17:24 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://REZuLt-525.github.io/p/the-mechanical-design-for-rm-sentry-robot-season-2024/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="a-brief-introduction-to--rm">A Brief Introduction to RM
&lt;/h1>&lt;p>The RoboMaster is a robotic competition held by the DJI and later on by the Committee of the Chinese university robot competition.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In the The RoboMaster University Championship (RMUC) , participating teams will independently develop different types of robots with various functions to face off on the battlefield. Each team’s participants will control their robots to attack the opponent’s robots and Base by launching projectiles. At the end of the match, the team with the highest remaining Base HP wins.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>There are overall 7 classes of robots: Hero, Infantry, Engineer, Sentry, Dart system, Radar system and Drone.&lt;/p>
&lt;h1 id="analysis-of-robot-performance-in-the-2023-season">Analysis of robot performance in the 2023 season
&lt;/h1>&lt;p>After the competition in 2023, conclusions about the first version of the robot have been drawn as:&lt;/p>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>Urgent need of lightweight design. The former robot have reached the weight limit of 28.5kg, thus some glass fiber boards have to use carbon fiber to reduce weight.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>The center of gravity of the robot head needs to be reconfigured. In 2023, the robot will run backwards when having the chassis and gimbal decoupled and the chassis rotating. This is because the magazine of the robot is placed on one side of the gimbal, leading to the gimbal&amp;rsquo;s center of gravity to shift to one side.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Stability and accuracy of the robot, such as launching accuracy and joint commissioning with the electronic control, need to be further polished and improved.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h1 id="the-iteration-of-the-sentry-robot-2024">The iteration of the sentry robot. 2024
&lt;/h1>&lt;p>Due to the analysis above, the sentry for 2024 season choose to make the following changes:&lt;/p>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>Change the position of the nacelle to center it on the yaw axis to reduce the moment of inertia.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>For the chassis, wheel sets are the heaviest parts. The wheel sets have 2 new versions to reduce weight. For the gimbal, more boards have undergone static analysis to further reduce weight.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Changed the design of the yaw axis to simplify the progress of changing the bearing.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;p>The new sentry also have changes to better performance:&lt;/p>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>For omnidirectional perception capability, a system consisting of a total of five cameras was designed on the yaw axis of the robot.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>The Next Unit of Computing(NUC) is replaced to balance the gimbal while lowering the center of gravity.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Suspension system are added and tuned to fit the working condition.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h1 id="images-of-the-robot">Images of the robot
&lt;/h1>&lt;img src="https://REZuLt-525.github.io/images/sentry2024_1.png" alt="123" width="300" height="200">
&lt;img src="https://REZuLt-525.github.io/images/sentry2024.jpg" alt="123" width="360" height="200">
&lt;img src="https://REZuLt-525.github.io/images/sentry2024_2.png" alt="123" width="305" height="200">
&lt;p>related images: sentry v5(left), image of sentry v4(middle), sentry v4(right)&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The mechanical design for synchro-drive wheel sets</title><link>https://REZuLt-525.github.io/p/the-mechanical-design-for-synchro-drive-wheel-sets/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 20:17:24 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://REZuLt-525.github.io/p/the-mechanical-design-for-synchro-drive-wheel-sets/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="brief-introduction-to-the-wheel-set">Brief introduction to the wheel set
&lt;/h1>&lt;p>The wheel set have undergone four major versions. The first version is using the suspension system on the driving part of the wheel set. This is because by using this watt linkage version, the heading part of the set can be linked to the frame of the chassis more solidly. Additionally, this can also reduce the mass weight under the spring, which can also improve the high speed performance of the robot. During the design of the watt linkage, I have taken mechanical simulation that when the rods are 60mm in length, the wheel in the midterm of the second rod can reach 42.7117mm on the y axis when the movement on the x axis is less than ±0.1mm. So this design can leave the suspension suspension system enough length to press the spring while keep the positioning of the wheel sets stable. The material of the rods are FR4 fiberglass panel, which is relatively cheaper in comparison to carbon fiber panel, while maintaining enough stiffness.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The second version was designed to maintain the robustness of the robot in the competition. During the test, the shafting design on the rods, with plug-in pots used as axles broke frequently under pressure tests. Additionally, since the driving part of the wheel set is somehow working as cantilever beams, the design of the first version may well separate under high impact. So in this version, the watt linkage was canceled, and two copper column to enhance stiffness. The thickness and the diameter of the wheel is the same as the first version, which is 20mm in width and 130mm in diameter. With an over-molding hardness of 90A and a thickness of 7.5mm, the robot can achieve fluent movement on asphalt, mastic and tile floors.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The first two versions of the wheels are finished in 2023 season. After the test of the season, the cons of these design can be summarized as these 4 points. Firstly, the wheel sets are overweight. The two versions share a mass weight of about 2.2kg, which cause the overall weight of the robot reach 25kg, furthermore causing the acceleration of the robot about 15% less than that of other universities’. Secondly, the torque of the M3508 P19 motor is too much for this working condition. Though a bigger torque of the driving motor can enable the acceleration from static state quicker, the maximum speed of the robot was somehow limited. Thirdly, since the total length of the M3508 motor reach 98.4mm, the rotational radius of the wheel set reach 71mm, which is about 12.5mm bigger than the wheel radius. Finally, there are no hub motors available which both fit the need of volume, weight and torque.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>So in summer 2023, I redesigned the wheel set to the third version. In this progress, the goal of design is focused on the integration of parts and the simplify of the design. In this version, expansion sleeve is used to take the place of D-shaped coupling, and metal right-angle adapter are used to enhance the stiffness of the diving part. Furthermore, the number of bearings have been reduced from 3 sets to 2, and later on 1 set. This can also help reduce the processing accuracy requirements of the computer numerical control(CNC) parts. Together with the integration of the rim, side plate and the expansion sleeve fixing CNC parts, this redesigning managed both the simplification of the wheel set and reducing cost. For the hardness of over-molding, since the thickness of over-molding have been reduced to 5mm, the hardness have also been changed to 60A to ensure enough traction. For the overweight problem, this version have achieved 45.5% weight reduction, and have a mass weight of 1.261kg.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The final version of the wheel consider only using the driving part of the motor. To further simplifying the design and ensure that under designed working conditions the motor can be working in a more sufficient state, this version chose to integrate the main body of the driving part of the wheel, and using the gearbox to cancel the design of coupling. In other words, I tried to design a hub motor. For the driving part, since the original motor is GM6020 hollow motor with a status torque of 1.2Nm and there seems to have a matched torque between that and that needed, the gear-ring gearbox’s ratio is 1:7. So the torque is 1.105Nm, and this design can leave enough space for the magnetic encoder and slip ring. The PCB design, serving as the magnetic encoder and the wheel distribution board, have rubber shock-absorption gaskets to ensure that under working conditions the two board will not separate and cause oscillation. Since the motor on this version is carried on a 3mm thick VMA board, the distance between boards is 7mm, leaving enough space for the gaskets and plug bolts. Along with the two double slot board-to-board connectors, the two PCB have five joints to keep stable and aligned.&lt;/p>
&lt;h1 id="images-of-the-design">Images of the design
&lt;/h1>&lt;img src="https://REZuLt-525.github.io/images/gbv1.png" alt="123" width="350" height="200">
&lt;img src="https://REZuLt-525.github.io/images/gbv2.png" alt="123" width="322" height="200">
&lt;img src="https://REZuLt-525.github.io/images/gbv3.png" alt="123" width="300" height="200">
&lt;img src="https://REZuLt-525.github.io/images/gbv4.jpg" alt="123" width="287" height="200">
&lt;p>The image of the design of the 4 versions of the synchro-drive wheel sets, v1 ~ v4 respectively.&lt;/p>
&lt;img src="https://REZuLt-525.github.io/images/gb5.png" alt="123" width="400" height="200">
&lt;img src="https://REZuLt-525.github.io/images/gb6.png" alt="123" width="462" height="200">
&lt;p>The exploded view and the design of the heading part of the version 4 of the synchro-drive wheel set.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The mechanical design for the planetary gearbox</title><link>https://REZuLt-525.github.io/p/the-mechanical-design-for-the-planetary-gearbox/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 20:17:24 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://REZuLt-525.github.io/p/the-mechanical-design-for-the-planetary-gearbox/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="a-brief-introduction-to-the-gearbox-design">A Brief Introduction to the gearbox design
&lt;/h1>&lt;p>The necessity of designing the gearbox is listed in chapter 3.2.2. Since the original gear ratio is 1:19 and the ratio should be or close to an odd integer, the first ratio was chosen as 9 or 11. Firstly the type of the gearbox was chosen as cycloid reduction gearbox for this type can achieve a big reduction ratio using a little space. But when designing, the standard parts limit the design. Balancing pros and cons, the design was later on changed to planetary gearbox to achieve a simpler structure. Since it is a 2K-H type gearbox, so with m = 0.6 and the number of teeth on the ring of 186, the diameter of the ring will reach about 130mm and disturb the design of the wheel diameter. Due to the ratio function of the second-stage gearbox, so when the teeth of the gear is 53 and 31 respectively, the final ratio is 10.1574.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>After the project of &amp;ldquo;High-dynamic, wheeled-legged bipedal robot system based on an LQR framework for Whole Body Control.&amp;rdquo;, the actual torque needed for a robot about 20kg in weight can be read directly from the hub motor. Working backwards, the torque should be about 1.5Nm. So in the planetary version, the ring have 119 teeth. In this version, the single-sided hub can also act as an outer retaining edge for the bearings, so it is possible to make the entire reduction gearbox part of the wheel.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>All parts of the gearbox is made by 6061-T6, a somehow extreme design because of the limit of budget. Due to the starting torque formula, the starting torque of the M3508 motor’s should be 4.4Nm, thus that of the driving part’s should be 0.232Nm. Furthermore, the gear’s thickness is 4mm. Sufficient redundancy has been considered.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>For the outcome of this design, the rotate time reduce from 1s to 0.3s in comparison to the Mecanum Wheel version of the robot under about the same working conditions.&lt;/p>
&lt;h1 id="images-of-the-robot">Images of the robot
&lt;/h1>&lt;img src="https://REZuLt-525.github.io/images/gearbox.jpg" alt="123" width="275" height="200">
&lt;img src="https://REZuLt-525.github.io/images/gearbox_2.png" alt="123" width="700" height="200">
&lt;p>The nylon proofing and exploded view of gearbox assembly&lt;/p>
&lt;h1 id="related-videos">Related videos
&lt;/h1>&lt;p>&lt;video src="https://REZuLt-525.github.io/images/inf2024_3.mp4" controls="controls" width="500" height="300">&lt;/video>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The video of Infantry rotating under 100W power limit of the chassis. The rotating speed of 0.3s per round is taken from this video.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Archives</title><link>https://REZuLt-525.github.io/archives/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://REZuLt-525.github.io/archives/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Links</title><link>https://REZuLt-525.github.io/links/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://REZuLt-525.github.io/links/</guid><description>&lt;p>To use this feature, add &lt;code>links&lt;/code> section to frontmatter.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This page&amp;rsquo;s frontmatter:&lt;/p>
&lt;div class="highlight">&lt;div class="chroma">
&lt;table class="lntable">&lt;tr>&lt;td class="lntd">
&lt;pre tabindex="0" class="chroma">&lt;code>&lt;span class="lnt">1
&lt;/span>&lt;span class="lnt">2
&lt;/span>&lt;span class="lnt">3
&lt;/span>&lt;span class="lnt">4
&lt;/span>&lt;span class="lnt">5
&lt;/span>&lt;span class="lnt">6
&lt;/span>&lt;span class="lnt">7
&lt;/span>&lt;span class="lnt">8
&lt;/span>&lt;span class="lnt">9
&lt;/span>&lt;/code>&lt;/pre>&lt;/td>
&lt;td class="lntd">
&lt;pre tabindex="0" class="chroma">&lt;code class="language-yaml" data-lang="yaml">&lt;span class="line">&lt;span class="cl">&lt;span class="nt">links&lt;/span>&lt;span class="p">:&lt;/span>&lt;span class="w">
&lt;/span>&lt;/span>&lt;/span>&lt;span class="line">&lt;span class="cl">&lt;span class="w"> &lt;/span>- &lt;span class="nt">title&lt;/span>&lt;span class="p">:&lt;/span>&lt;span class="w"> &lt;/span>&lt;span class="l">GitHub&lt;/span>&lt;span class="w">
&lt;/span>&lt;/span>&lt;/span>&lt;span class="line">&lt;span class="cl">&lt;span class="w"> &lt;/span>&lt;span class="nt">description&lt;/span>&lt;span class="p">:&lt;/span>&lt;span class="w"> &lt;/span>&lt;span class="l">GitHub is the world&amp;#39;s largest software development platform.&lt;/span>&lt;span class="w">
&lt;/span>&lt;/span>&lt;/span>&lt;span class="line">&lt;span class="cl">&lt;span class="w"> &lt;/span>&lt;span class="nt">website&lt;/span>&lt;span class="p">:&lt;/span>&lt;span class="w"> &lt;/span>&lt;span class="l">https://github.com&lt;/span>&lt;span class="w">
&lt;/span>&lt;/span>&lt;/span>&lt;span class="line">&lt;span class="cl">&lt;span class="w"> &lt;/span>&lt;span class="nt">image&lt;/span>&lt;span class="p">:&lt;/span>&lt;span class="w"> &lt;/span>&lt;span class="l">https://github.githubassets.com/images/modules/logos_page/GitHub-Mark.png&lt;/span>&lt;span class="w">
&lt;/span>&lt;/span>&lt;/span>&lt;span class="line">&lt;span class="cl">&lt;span class="w"> &lt;/span>- &lt;span class="nt">title&lt;/span>&lt;span class="p">:&lt;/span>&lt;span class="w"> &lt;/span>&lt;span class="l">TypeScript&lt;/span>&lt;span class="w">
&lt;/span>&lt;/span>&lt;/span>&lt;span class="line">&lt;span class="cl">&lt;span class="w"> &lt;/span>&lt;span class="nt">description&lt;/span>&lt;span class="p">:&lt;/span>&lt;span class="w"> &lt;/span>&lt;span class="l">TypeScript is a typed superset of JavaScript that compiles to plain JavaScript.&lt;/span>&lt;span class="w">
&lt;/span>&lt;/span>&lt;/span>&lt;span class="line">&lt;span class="cl">&lt;span class="w"> &lt;/span>&lt;span class="nt">website&lt;/span>&lt;span class="p">:&lt;/span>&lt;span class="w"> &lt;/span>&lt;span class="l">https://www.typescriptlang.org&lt;/span>&lt;span class="w">
&lt;/span>&lt;/span>&lt;/span>&lt;span class="line">&lt;span class="cl">&lt;span class="w"> &lt;/span>&lt;span class="nt">image&lt;/span>&lt;span class="p">:&lt;/span>&lt;span class="w"> &lt;/span>&lt;span class="l">ts-logo-128.jpg&lt;/span>&lt;span class="w">
&lt;/span>&lt;/span>&lt;/span>&lt;/code>&lt;/pre>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>&lt;/table>
&lt;/div>
&lt;/div>&lt;p>&lt;code>image&lt;/code> field accepts both local and external images.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Search</title><link>https://REZuLt-525.github.io/search/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://REZuLt-525.github.io/search/</guid><description/></item><item><title>关于</title><link>https://REZuLt-525.github.io/%E5%85%B3%E4%BA%8E/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://REZuLt-525.github.io/%E5%85%B3%E4%BA%8E/</guid><description>&lt;p>This is a test page for i18n support.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>